virtualtrust.net 2016-11-07

# Virtualtrust LTD

## 6.2%-6.4% daily for 20 days

### Min deposit $10 - $500

#### We accept Perfectmoney,Payeer and Bitcoin

## 15%-20%  
daily for 10 days

### Min deposit $501 - $1,000

#### The best profitable investment program in the field! 

## 30%-40%  
daily for 5 days

### MINIMAL INVEST $1,001 - $2,000

#### BEST PLACE TO HAVE VIP ACCOUNT

## Operating since 2005

### 6% COMMISSION

#### FOR 2 LEVEL DEEP, WE OFFER REFERRAL COMMISSION

#### Want to be updated with our offers and news?

###### Read more +

### TRUST MANAGEMENT

Assets trust management represents one of the most popular operation methods in the world stock markets for companies as well as individuals. Among the advantages of assets trust management we may mention many.

###### Read more +

### WELL DOCUMENTED

Our company offers comprehensive services in investing free funds for gaining stable profits. We provide turn-key solutions for portfolio management, bookkeeping, report accountancy and information support.

###### Read more +

### GREAT SUPPORT

Our experienced portfolio managers will help any investor to assess his risks, select optimal investment strategies, disclose trade securities parameters, and agree on basic principles of portfolio management.

## PRIVACY & POLICY

#### These are our services that we're prowdly doing.

### **Information Collected**

All information collected is used solely by **Virtualtrust LTD**. Your privacy is important to us, which is why we will never trade or sell your personal information. We will collect your Personal Information such as your payment processor accounts and email address. This information will never be given to paying advertisers, since **Virtualtrust LTD** handles all E-Mailing itself.

### **Use of Information**

**Virtualtrust LTD** to contact you regarding updates to our program and provide payment to you using your Personal Information.

### **Links to Third Party Sites**

**Virtualtrust LTD** doesn't contain links to other Web Sites ("Linked Sites") except [Payeer.com](http://payeer.com/), [Perfectmony.com](http://perfectmony.is/) and [Coinpayment.net](http://coinpayment.net/) 

### **Acceptance**

By using this site, you agree to the Privacy Policy of **Virtualtrust LTD**. If you do not agree to this privacy policy, please do not use our sites. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time without notification to our Members. If any major updates take place, we will post the link at home page or Inform members by email.
